be.
I don't think it's all over,
but I don't think
it's all over,
but I don't think it's all
over.
Don't you know?
It's not me!
I I
I I I I I
I Ah, this is love, ah!
This is awesome!
Guys, check it out!
I'm like Saji!
What happened to your head?
It used to be so big and tall,
like you had a giant light
bulb growing out of your skull.
My head?
Oh, well, it had grown
quite long, you see.
So, I cut it.
What, like you had it snipped
off at the frickin' barber?
Then I had to.
What else was I to do?
When I last saw you, it was so big.
I was almost as tall as a giant.
I heard it was big, but
that sounds ridiculous.
It was like a balloon.
You cut your head, but you're still alive?
How is that even possible?
Well, you see, my young friends,
I have a brim-brim-brim.
Ew, I beat my tongue.
Oh, no, my poor tongue.
Uh, old man, you okay?
Ahem.
You see, my young friends,
I've eaten the brim-brim fruit.
It allows me to absorb
limitless knowledge,
but the more my brain knows, the
more it grows and grows and grows.
On top of my natural genius, I
possess an unlimited debtor bank.
Thus, I have the world's largest brain,
and it grows larger and larger every day.
Wait, what?
Then where is it?
That sounds insane. You lost me.
I get it.
You cut your brain out,
so now you're stupid.
Do not trifle with a genius, boy!
This apple here is an antenna!
Connected to what?
Look at the structure up there.
The inside of that egg doesn't
say punk records just for fun.
That is where my enormous brain is stored.
It's really that big?
Even when I'm far away,
I remain connected to it,
thanks to the brainwaves
received to this apple ten-up.
That's so cool!
So are you a doctor of
medicine too, Vegapunk?
You bet, little buddy.
You met a girl when you came here who
also called herself Vegapunk, yes?
Yes, she punched me in the face.
That girl is one of my clones.
There are six on the island. Two ninjas?
It's Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Each of them has a unique talent
and plays a necessary role.
Shaka is calm and conscientious.
Lilith has no morals and
is willing to plunder.
Edison is bursting with ideas.
The wise Pythagoras
follows the path of reason.
Atlas is here when violence is the answer.
And the greedy York
eats, poops, and sleeps.
They are me, in the sense that
they comprise my personality.
But they do six times the work.
I'm confused. Once daily,
they synchronize their
experiences and newly
acquired knowledge by
accessing punk records.
Their personalities and
missions are different,
making each of them uniquely
useful for my research.
All of you share the same brain?
This is far beyond my comprehension.
Just think of it as us
visiting the same library.
Let me give you an example.
Imagine if the rest of the
world accessed the database
and read the information
contained in my brain.
It would be as if all mankind
had acquired my knowledge.
Then what if those people updated punk
records with their personal discoveries,
just as I do?
Why, we could create a sea of
knowledge, far exceeding my own.
A library of the human experience.
Like a super brain,
shared by all humanity.
Does that mean I could study
medicine from all over the world?
That's the idea.
I have no idea what's going on!
But what happens when different
ideologies enter the brain?
Won't that cause issues?
A fine question, first son of the sea.
And yet, if we never dare to take a
chance, then science will never advance.
Of course you would think that way.
You bastard!
You'll sacrifice anything
for your research!
Or anyone, even!
Like my father.
You turned him into a heartless machine.
Stop, Bonnie.
That beam saber is a
failed invention. Shut up.
It'll kill you just fine.
Please calm down, Bonnie.
You must think this through.
I know that you're angry, but killing
him will make far too many enemies.
I don't give a damn.
You're going to turn my
father back, Or I swear,
I'm gonna slice your head
off right here and now!
Please turn off the switch, quickly!
What?
It burns!
But it attracts a swarm of fire!
Bonnie!
Hey, Bonnie! Bonnie! Wake up!
Check this out!
Put that down!
She'll freak out!
What happens if she dies of shock?
Hmm?
If that weapon wasn't a
failure, I would likely be dead.
But it's no wonder.
I can't blame her.
It's only natural that
she'd want to kill me.
Oh, there was something I wanted to ask.
I heard you came here
from the land of Varno.
Mm-hmm.
I also heard there were two dragons, dear.
Kaido and someone else. Oh, yeah.
That's my friend Momo.
I see.
It seems he ate a failed synthetic
Devil Fruit I left at Punk Hazard.
Oh, that's cool.
Wait, how did it fail?
It wasn't from lack of effort.
I developed that project myself.
Twenty years of hard work and a
whole mountain of research money.
I tried to make a fruit from
Kaido's bloodline elements.
But in the end, I couldn't get
the composition quite right.
Oh, so that's why he was
able to transform like Kaido.
It wasn't a failure.
He breathes fire and he's real strong.
He protects the land of Wano now.
You did a really good job, apple guy.
What is the dragon's color? Pink way.
Failure!
An utter failure!
What's wrong with him?
He's a genius, but he's also
quite the perfectionist.
Oh, yeah!
Hey, old man!
Can you get this to move?
You're the one who made it, right?
I didn't make it.
This is the legendary
iron giant that is said
to have attacked Marie Joie 200 years ago.
They've attacked Marie Joie?
That's insane! Indubitably!
This monstrosity was
built 900 years ago! 900?
Forgive my skepticism,
but how can that be?
Wow, you're really special, big guy!
So how did you attack Marie
Joie? Cannons? Lasers?
Come on!
Wake up, Robo-nose gay!
Do robot stuff!
Get up, boys! Shoot lasers! Let's go!
That is an antique, you trogglingite!
Quite a fascinating story.
But tell me, why would the
Iron Giant attack Marie Joie?
A fine question!
I have it the faintest clue.
Oh.
I heard that it ran out of power
and no damage was starting.
Regardless, I imagine its very existence
was shocking to the scientists of the time.
It's extraordinary.
Beyond any technology in its era.
Hundreds of years later, I'd say
this is still quite the shock.
They were trying to wake it up, but it
might be better if it stays like this.
It could be dangerous.
No one knows where this iron
giant came from, after all.
It's unclear what it was trying
to do or what it was capable of.
As for the world government, predictably
they ordered its destruction.
But the scientists of
that age protected it.
They hid it away where
no one could find it.
And to this day, no one knows it is here.
Not even the government itself.
Anyway, I'm surprised you
made it to this junkyard.
The entrance to here
looks like a normal wall.
I can't imagine how you found your way in.
Where'd he go?
He just vanished.
I got turned old.
My brain wasn't working right.
I mean it's terrible.
Hey, that sounds concerning!
200 years ago?
That's the year fishmen were
granted citizens' rights.
I don't know how the robot works.
Are you saying it climbed all the way up?
The red line?
So it seems.
Am I crazy?
Or does that thing look an awful lot
like the robot that brought us here?
That's right.
It's no coincidence.
Vega Force One was modeled
after the Iron Giant.
But even with all my knowledge, there
was one thing I couldn't replicate.
But you're the brainiest
bro on the entire planet.
What the hell does it take to stump you?
The power source.
The way the Iron Giant used energy defies
our modern understanding of science.
By the way, I'm glad Luffy and the others
are all right, but who's that woman?
That's Jewelry Bonnie. She's
a pirate. Wait a second.
That's not the same little
girl we saved earlier, is it?
Huh?
I'm sorry, what is going
on with Vegapunk's head?
Is Bonnie okay? What gives?
Poor Bonnie.
She's been through so much.
Yeah, because of you.
She should get to hit you.
What the hell do you know about this, huh?
That's a scene!
When she wakes up, there's something
important I need to give her.
But first, I have a favor to ask.
It's extremely fortunate that
you showed up here when you did.
You might even call it fate.
What do you mean?
I need you to take me away from Egghead.
I need Quasar, your help!
Huh?
This is Cipher Palace speaking.
Grant us entry to the island at once.
Do you copy?
I said this is Cipher Palace.
Oh, no, no.
This is bad.
This is very bad!
Attack!
Should have trained their pets better.
We're not cool!
We received a report.
It seems that Jewelry
Bonnie is here on Egghead.
Well, that's convenient.
Don't let her escape again. Go!
She's outlived her usefulness.
Be sure to kill her on sight.
Chaka, a government ship just arrived!
What? Why?
You pirates need to hide!
If the government finds out
you're here, we're all doomed!
No complaints from us.
We're not looking to pick a fight
with them, just to be clear.
As you shouldn't!
They have CP Zero with them!
Even Rob Lucci is on board!
What?
Rob Lucci?
I guess it's time to feed the cat. Huh?
Oh, and look, we've got
five tuna steaks here.
Come on, let's hand these goofballs over.
Let me out of these shoes
right now, you sick bastard!
No!
Why is he here?
I thought he quit his job!
We can't let him get in!
You better not even try!
I'll send him packing myself!
Don't worry, Robin, you're safe with us.
We'll beat him as many times as it takes.
Thank you.
Officially, they're here
to return the seraphim.
Tell them to leave it and
send them away. Excuse me?
We're going to bar the government's entry.
Lock down the island!
Wait, stop!
You're still under repair!
You can't start moving now!
Dragon, help!
There's something wrong with Kuma!
Huh? Kuma?
Stop, Kuma! What happened?
Maybe the Navy is still
giving him orders somehow!
What do you need?
Let us help you!
Can you at least tell us
where you're trying to go?
What started this? I don't know!
He just got up out of the blue!
He's not supposed to
have any free will left!
Kuma! Stop it!
You're gonna hurt yourself!
Come back here, Kuma!
Where are you going?
Kuma! Kuma!
We need you, Kuma!
You're part of our family!
We have to stick together
and see our battle through!
No, Goomba, stop!
Please, don't go!
He's gone.
Thank you for returning
our seraphim to us.
Unfortunately, your request
for entry is denied!
So just drop him off and go please.
Uh, Noni Dory S Bear can return
home on his own from there.
He'll have to forgive us but we are
so busy we can barely think straight.
So um, order S Bear to
return, and you can call it a day.
Mission complete.
Thank you for your service.
Whoa there, you can't
just leave us out in the cold.
Seems they're wrong to us.
Aren't you at least going to
invite us in for a cup of tea?
We've been sailing for days.
We're freezing out here.
Naval Branch G-14 is
right around the corner.
I'm sure they'll welcome
you with open arms.
Am I speaking to Vegapunk? Yes.
I have a question for you, Doctor.
What do you know about the
Egghead disappearances?
Disappearances?
I beg your pardon?
I'm afraid I don't follow.
Two months ago, Cipher Pole No.
5's ship vanished into thin air.
A month ago, it was Cipher Pole No. 7.
Two weeks ago, Cipher Pole No. 8.
Quite the strange coincidence. In fact,
not one government ship that has visited
Egghead in the past two
months has returned.
I was hoping you might be able
to shed some light on why.
Well, I am so sorry to hear that, but
rest assured we don't have them here.
My records show that all vessels
have shipped out in ship shape!
Hey, what exactly are you implying?
Are you trying to say we've been messing
with those ships, you overgrown house cat?
Go to hell!
Lilith, I know you're evil, but
please don't antagonize him?
You are going to look so stupid
when I open this port! Lilith, no!
Back up, Pythagoras!
Ah, well, my gosh, there's no ship
here, but we appreciate your visit.
Goodbye.
Fine, then, if you insist. Go.
Nice try, but I doubt
they're going to budge.
Shall we move on to plan B?
Everyone, get ready.
We're going to abandon ship.
We'll use the Seraphim.
Hesper follows our orders.
We'll have it transport us to Egghead.
We're sacrificing the ship.
As soon as we leave it will fall
prey to the sea beast weapons
That's a tad bit risky, don't you think?
Impatience isn't attractive
in a man, you know?
If you want to be swallowed by the sea,
you're welcome to stay and threats to!
Let's go
You want to leave this place, old man?
But it's your lab.
I thought you liked living here.
What's not to like?
Why, I'm creating the future itself here.
I can use government facilities
and funds however I please.
And thus, my research has
continued at an extraordinary pace.
You've seen only a small
fraction of my work.
My brain is a fountain of
ideas that never stops flowing.
But there's not enough
time, not enough help,
not enough money to make
my true dream a reality.
You mean you're planning
something even bigger?
You want to know what it is?
You probably do!
When it happens, the whole
universe will know my name.
Oh, is it another big robot?
Tell us, please!
Very well, then.
It's really quite simple.
I will use science to squash inequality.
I will create a world where
free energy is provided to all!
That's not the reaction
I expected. I don't know.
Free stuff's cool, I guess.
That would be a worthwhile
endeavor if you could achieve it.
Most wars are fought over energy.
We might be able to achieve world
peace, but resources are too limited.
Are they limited?
Or is it mankind who is limited?
Energy is everywhere.
You can feel it in the air, in
the ground, it's all around us.
It's simply overflowing.
The world is full of energy.
All we need to do is convert
it into tangible power.
Inequality will become
a thing of the past.
Wars will come to an end.
With the power of science, we
can make this world a utopia.
Still not interested?
No, I think it's really cool that
you want to make people happy.
But hero stuff just isn't my thing.
Anyway, you never said
why you want to leave.
Well, I have a problem.
The more I try to create this energy,
the further I delve into lost history.
For example,
I can't help but to look to our
giant mechanical friend here
and wonder what kind of ancient
energy source powered him.
It is the nature of a scientist
to remain curious after all.
So I took a little peek into history
and unraveled some forbidden truths.
I was only carrying on my friend's will,
but it took me deep into dangerous waters.
And that's my story.
I just left learning too much.
Now the government will erase me.
Just like Aura.
This can't be good.
It must be CP0.
Wait, Zero?
They're a spy organization directly under
the orders of the Celestial Dragons.
I thought they were called CP9.
Did they change their name or what?
CP0 is a higher rank.
You rarely see them make a move.
But when they do, it means that the
course of history is about to change.
This place is incredible!
Why, I've never seen anything like it!
It's unreal, like we stepped
straight into the future!
I'm getting a little fired up here.
What's Cypherpole doing here?
And why aren't they
wearing their black suits?
How bizarre.
Don't they usually come
in through the port?
Hey, guys!
We just got a report that two of the Sea
Beast weapons were attacked at the shore!
Don't tell me.
Does that mean...
they're intruders?
Shaka, CP0 is on the island.
We're too late! They're here!
Luchi's being a giant pain in the ass.
What else is new, cat bastard?
Come on!
Give it up already, Luchi!
I'm still stuck!
Would you fix these stupid
future shoes already?
I need my damn feet!
How else can I keep Robin safe?
How did they come ashore so quickly?
Well, definitely not by ship.
That's for darn sure.
Seems they realized the
Sea Beast weapons would
attack their ship as soon
as they refused to leave.
They must have used the
Seraphim's Papa power to fly here.
What should we do?
How resourceful.
They must really want to fight if
they're sacrificing their ship.
Very well.
If that's what you desire.
Sound the alarm!
We need to evacuate the citizens!
Roger that!
Tell Atlas to return to the lab.
Prepare all of the Seraphim for combat.
Sentomaru will lead them.
Releasing Seraphim number one.
S .Hawk.
Releasing Seraphim, number three, S-Snake.
Releasing Seraphim, number four, S-Shark.
Deploy!
If the world government has
decided they want to kill me,
then I don't have much time left.
CP0 is here, so I need to pack my bags.
Now please honor my requaser
and take me out to sea with you.
You make it sound like we're all
just going on a picnic or something.
If you disappear, it'll be big news.
This might put an even
bigger target on our backs.
Okay, your head looks funny, so why not?
Is that a reason?
Splendid.
Somehow I had a feeling you'd say yes.
All right, let us go.
This will be a battlefield soon.
For starters, please bring Bonnie
to the Lobby face above the clouds.
How do we get up there?
It should be easy.
Just take the vacuum rocket.
You can find it down
here in the Fabrio face.
What's a vacuum rocket?
That sounds cool!
Well, don't dawdle now, boys.
See you in the sky in the blink of an eye.
He disappeared!
You're awesome, Mr. Appelman!
I'm finding the future
to be very confusing.
Hey, take a gander at that.
It's a giant monster!
Damn it!
It won't die!
The force go right through it!
Of course they do.
This island is full of technical
marvels beyond your wildest imagination.
If you think your guns will
work here, you've been had.
I've always wanted to
fight something like you.
Something untouchable.
And I know why they couldn't hurt you.
Because you're from outer space!
Prepare yourself, alien fiend!
It must have some sort
of space physiology.
It's no use.
I'm not giving up. Well, you should.
It's a hologram.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Have you perhaps been here before?
Let's say it's nostalgic.
Well, I'm already up here.
I might as well check out whatever
this thing is above the clouds.
Chances are that's where
Vegapunk is hiding.
Tell me, Luchi, do you see those yellow
lines way up there in the clouds?
Yes.
Watch what happens when
someone crosses them.
Laser beams automatically fire on them.
It's a defensive system
called the Frontier Dome.
It encircles the labophase,
guarding in all directions.
The lesson here is not to underestimate
the world's greatest scientist.
You really should have told him that.
Stussy!
How could you just stand
there and watch me fry?
Warms you up faster than tea.
What the hell are you assholes doing?
You think you can come into my lab?
And be more violent than me?
Punk-ass pig!
Time to die!
I'll try!
Alright, this place is officially insane.
Is that one a hologram too?
Oh, no.
This young lady is Atlas.
She's one of the Vegapunks.
Look, it's Atlas! Atlas!
Abort mission immediately.
Mighty!
Very well, then.
Six-King Pistol!
Oh no Atlas! She's down!
Merciless as ever, isn't he?
It beat her in one shot?
This guy's seriously scary!
What's going on?
Why is Cypherball attacking us?
We both work for the government,
so we're allies, aren't we?
Attention, Fabriophase.
Evacuate the lab immediately.
Good evacuation, Jonas.
We have to go right to the factory!
Evacuate now.
We are under attack.
She's still alive, but barely.
Let's eliminate her while
we have the opportunity.
Rocky, run!
First you gotta find it, then we fly!
Hehehe!
Uh!
Straw Hat!
I'm laughing at you.
I'm the same.
I'm the same. I'm the same.
I'm not even.
I don't forget.
I'm the same.